Manay Bhaysar

+916355501063|manav.bhavsar28@gmail.com | http://www.linkedin.com/in/bhavsar-manav

SUMMARY

Self-motivated recent graduate with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science Engineering (Al & ML). Possesses a strong foundation in programming, software development, and IT principles. Experienced in working with various programming languages such as Java, Python, C and PHP. Demonstrates excellent problem-solving abilities, attention to detail, and a passion for technology and continuous learning.

EDUCATION

B.E. - Computer Science Engineering

Aug 2020 - Jun 2024

New LJ Institute of Engineering and Technology, Ahmedabad

CGPA: 8.76 | CPI: 8.37

EXPERIENCE

Intern at Code-Unnati Center of Excellence

Jan 2024 - Apr 2024

Edunet Foundation, Ahmedabad

- As an intern I learned about Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, IOT and SAP
- In this Internship I developed a project of Resume analyzer using Python and its I ibararies
- Have hands-on practice on RasberryPi.

Data Analyst and Machine learning intern

Jul 2023 - Aug 2023

Infolabz, Ahmedabad

- My role was to use json and extract api into python dictionary and perform Machine Learning models on it.
- Machine Learning Model which were used in data analysis are Classification, Regression and Clustering.
- In this Internship I developed a Machine Learning project called Image Classifier using Python and its Libraries.

SKILLS

Python, Java, C, HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, MySQL.

PROJECTS

Al Resume Analyzer

- An AI resume analyzer is an advanced software tool designed to streamline the
 recruitment process by automatically reviewing and evaluating resumes. Utilizing
 natural language processing (NLP) and machine learning algorithms, it can parse
 through resumes to extract relevant information, assess candidate qualifications, and
 match them against job requirements.
- Tools: Python for Backend, HTML, CSS and StreamLit for Frontend.
- Database: MySQL.
- Main Libraries used in this project are NLTK and spaCy library.

Image Classifier

 An image classifier is a type of artificial intelligence (AI) system designed to automatically categorize and label images into predefined classes or categories.
 Leveraging techniques from computer vision and machine learning, particularly deep learning, image classifiers analyze visual content to identify patterns and features that distinguish different objects or scenes.

- Tools: Python, Convolution Neural Network (CNN), it is essential for feature extraction and image analysis.
- Main Libraries used are Tensorflow, Tensorflow keras and numpy

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning Vodafone India Services Pvt. Ltd.

2022